perfiliate.com 2012-03-24

# PRIVACY POLICY

## Perfiliate Technologies Limited

(Company Number 3783384) trading as buy.at whose registered office is at 

Shropshire House,   
11-20 Capper Street,   
London,   
WC1E 6JAis committed to safeguarding the privacy of its users. 

We take your privacy very seriously and it is important to us that you can use and enjoy the website without having to compromise your privacy in any way.  Perfiliate Technologies Limited is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998  (Registration Number Z7349922) 

The purpose of this policy is to explain how we will use and process your personal data. 

## What information do we collect? 

We will ask you to provide information on our website during the registration process as an affiliate.If you contact us we may keep a copy of that correspondence. 

The type of information which we may collect about you includes your: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Phone number 
  * Fax number 
  * Email address 
  * Bank Details 

## How is the information used? 

We use your information to enable us to improve our marketing, for purposes of administering our business activities, making available other products and services to our clients and potential clients. We will show the information you provide to such of our employees as need to see it. 

We also use information in aggregated form (where no individual user is identified).  This information may include: 

  * the URL which you came from 
  * the URL you next go to
  * what browser and operating system you are using 
  * your IP address 

This information is used for market research, to customise our site content and we believe that this allows us to monitor and improve our site and tailor it to better meet our users requirements. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify an individual. 

##  Use of Cookies 

Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on a user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one web page to simplify subsequent transactions or to short cut access to the site. We use cookies to track clicks, sales and leads and for member log in sessions. On certain sites or third party sites we may utilise cookies for other purposes such as order tracking in online shops or for targeting advertisements to particular types of visitor. 

##  Use of Tracking Beacons

buy.at also utilises an Internet technology commonly called a "Beacon." This technology is also referred to as "Tracking Pixels", "action tags" or "transparent gifs". If the merchant chooses to use tracking pixel technology, the merchant’s web page will contain a clear gif, which would not be visible to the user. Merchants program the Tracking Pixel via Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) to collect certain information about your visit to their web site. This information can rarely contain personally identifiable information about you (please refer to Who do we share the information with?). This information is returned to buy.at for processing. Our web beacons are usually placed on our clients' websites, and occasionally, we place our Tracking Pixels on our clients' partners' websites. We also take efforts to have these web sites disclose the presence of our Tracking Pixels.

## Who do we share the information with? 

We may also disclose your personal data to: 

  * any law enforcement agency requesting it in connection with the commission of an offence; 
  * comply with applicable laws and lawful government and/or regulatory requests; 
  * protect our systems and ourselves; and/or 
  * operate our systems properly 

##  Merchants, Affiliates and Causes 

We reserve the right to and you agree that we may disclose any information, which we hold about you to any government, regulatory, criminal investigatory or other authorised body such as the police, Customs and Excise and trading standards officers without notice to you and without incurring liability to you in connection with any investigation of fraud, infringement of intellectual property rights or illegal activity or in relation to any matter, which may expose us to legal liability or otherwise. 

We do not sell, trade, give away or rent your personal information to third parties unless you tell us you are happy for us to do so.  We may provide statistics on an aggregated basis but these will not include any personally identifiable information. 

##  How do we safeguard your personal data? 

The internet is not a secure medium however we use industry standard safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your personal data such as passwords, encryption keys and firewalls. 

Your personal information will be held securely in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

Our security systems mean that we may request proof of identity before we are able to disclose information to you. 

##  Marketing 

We will send you a newsletter to the address you provided to us when you registered. You may ask us to remove your details from our database at any time by writing to us at the address below, emailing us at [privacy@buy.at](mailto:privacy@buy.at) or via the Management Area. 

##  Your consent 

By submitting your information and by using our website you consent to the collection and use of personal information relating to you as set out in this privacy policy. If we decide to amend our privacy policy we shall post any changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect how we use it and under what circumstance we disclose it. Please check back regularly. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. 

##  Transfers 

The information you provide may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers. 

##  How can you correct any inaccuracies? 

We are committed to ensuring that the information which we hold about you is accurate and up to date.  You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us at privacy@buy.at You are entitled to a copy of your information held by us: we may make a small charge for providing this to you. 

Please notify us if you find any inaccuracies providing us with sufficient information to identify you, so that any errors can be corrected. 

You agree to keep your data accurate and up to date and promptly to send us any new or revised personal data. 

You warrant and undertake to us that all of the details you supply to us are true and accurate. 

##  Contacting Us 

Any questions or comments relating to this statement or our site should be directed to us by sending an email to [privacy@buy.at](mailto:privacy@buy.at) or in writing to 

No 2 Cathedral Square,  
Cloth Market,   
Newcastle upon Tyne,  
NE1 1EH.

This page was last updated on 23rd April, 2007
